Hello everyone, tonight we are going to talk about the theme of our top change version, and then we will talk about two tops with a draw structure.
The first one is a smarker top, and the second one is a draw structure, which is the pink top we saw on the poster.
Okay, let's get started.
First, we insert the model.
Then insert the long-sleeve t-shirt.
This long-sleeve t-shirt is just an ordinary knit t-shirt.
Next,
we will modify the t-shirt into the style we want.
Here we first observe the structure of its shoulder.
At this time, its shoulder line is still relatively long.
Then we need to modify it.
You can use the mouse to roughly locate where you want to modify the shoulder line.
Then use the edit shape line tool in our 3D tool bar to adjust the shoulder line.
After adjustment, you need to look at the front of this effect.
Then we will adjust the length of the shirt.
Note that here we need to switch to this edit sheet tool.
After we select the line of the bottom, we pull it with the left key and then press the right key.
At this time, this moving distance spring will appear.
Enter the number.
After modifying the sheet, remember to simulate it.
Here I use the mouse to locate it.
We will simulate it.
Because we want to make a division in the front chest position,
we will use the mouse to point it out.
Then we look at the blue point.
At the 2D window, draw a line inside.
Use the inner multi-sided line tool.
After drawing this line, switch to the edit sheet tool and align it to the outside of the sheet.
Then we look at the inner line.
Let's look at the position of the inner line.
Here we switch this part of the 3D window to an opaque mode.
Here we can see more accurately where the inner line is on the model.
Change back to the surface of the濃密文理.
Let's adjust it again on the basis of the original inner line.
Here we need to align the front and back pieces,
and then draw the inner line of the front piece at the same time on the back piece.
And then align it to the outside of the board.
Let's put the board back.
Select the two inner lines and then do the inner line border.
The border is 40.
This border is set according to the style you want.
The number of borders is also set according to the length of the body and the structure you want.
Here we can select the two inner lines at the top and bottom,
and then do a cut and sew.
After the cut is done,
we can select the middle board and enlarge it.
The front and back pieces are the same.
Activate the center point in the middle of the double-click,
and then zoom in.
Right-click to enter the value of 120.
The front and back pieces are all 120.
First, widen the board,
and then we will shrink the middle.
Before shrinking, we need to determine the value after shrinking.
This value is determined by the body data of our model.
At the top,
the top menu bar,
here is the virtual model.
We can check the virtual model editor.
It contains the body data of the model,
chest, waist, and so on.
After knowing this data,
let's add elasticity to these inner lines.
Here we select the inner line closest to the BP point.
Enter the full length.
Now we can see that the ratio of these two inner lines in the selection is 65.
Then we can use the ratio of 65 directly,
and we don't need to set two lines and two lines.
And then we can use the ratio of 65 directly,
And then we can see that the ratio of 65 directly,
and we don't need to set two lines and two lines.
Other inner lines are the same.
After selecting the ratio,
open the elasticity and enter the ratio.
We can use the mouse to help us determine which inner line,
The internal line here is closer to the bottom of the chest, so the value entered here cannot be the 800 just now, and it needs to be set a little smaller.
The data entered here is the waist, but this 600 may be smaller, and then we will adjust the proportion of the elasticity.
This proportion is now 49, change it to 50, and then the rest of the internal line will use the proportion of 50.
Notice that the data we use here is model body data, but it is not absolute.
We need to determine the specific elasticity ratio based on the actual situation, such as the fabric we use, and the effect we want to achieve.
We can slowly modify it later.
The bottom edge of the sheet also needs to be set to the elasticity.
Let's simulate and see the current effect.
Here you can see that the chest is still tight, but the waist is more relaxed.
The model posture becomes a stoop is for the better observation of the middle.
Let's look at the structure of the stoop.
We will feeling the front load
pain
You can tighten your waist a little bit here.
According to the structure of our human body,
the waist is the tightest here,
and then the waist goes down,
and it will gradually expand near the hip.
After adding the elasticity,
in order to better see the effect of the draw,
we need to reduce its particle diameter a little bit.
Here, we only reduced the front and back of the draw.
The particle diameter of other plates is still relatively large.
Don't modify it first.
We need to reduce the length from the center of our body.
Now we would like to do a shoulder split.
Do a shoulder split.
That would be to lengthen the straight edge of the body,
and the waist would become closer to the ground.
We can now make a shoulder split.
And we can also do a shoulder split.
Change the inner line of 10 or 15 to 15
The back can be made wider
Make two inner lines first
Then right-click to cut and sew
Here we always use the edit tool
Choose the two lines near the border
Then right-click to merge them
After merging, this structure will be a little bit uneven
Then we can adjust it again
Change this point to a free curve point
Then edit this curve
These extra curve points can be deleted
Here can be deleted directly
Then next
Let's do the expansion of this front piece
The same is the activation center point
Then pull it wide
Here is 125%
The particle diameter of this plate is relatively large
So its draw effect is not very obvious
The back is the same
Under the simulation state, adjust its shape
Here you can add a seam allowance to it
Then set the intensity to a little bigger
Just like this
Then this short plate
It won't be pulled by this long plate
Can be better
Maintain the shape of the seam
Next we will give the shoulder here
This is the shoulder
So we will add a seam allowance
So we will have the shoulder here
And then we will make the shoulder
Then we will do the seam allowance
Next, we are going to expand the shoulder here.
Then mark it first to make a division point.
Because what we want is to make a fold effect at the top of his sleeve.
So we have to set these two divisions first.
Change to the edit board tool, change the unwanted points.
Because the later expansion will lead to the change of the sewing line.
Here we need to first cut the sewing line into two sections.
Delete the original.
Then cut the sewing line into two sections according to this division point.
Here we use the free sewing tool.
Let's try again.
Give it a try.
Then use the extension tool.
Here we use the extension board line.
I will choose all the directions.
Here we set the distance of movement.
That is to say, on the basis of the original line section, increase 120, line section 2, increase 80.
After extension, the shape of this sheet will be a little deformed.
At this time, we need to use the edit curve point to adjust this line section.
The same is to delete the excess curve points.
Adjust the line here to make it rounder.
For the sleeve, we directly turn it into a straight line and delete its original curve point.
Here, we make a 20 mm inner line to make it easier for us to sew the back of the sleeve to make a fold here.
First, smooth the sleeve.
Make a 20 mm flat line extension.
Then fold in the extended part.
The fold line should be 0 degrees.
Here we make a 170 mm wide, 20 mm high.
This is a gold-plated line.
This width is according to the requirement.
After making a symmetrical line, make a seam allowance.
This seam allowance needs to be changed to a fold.
We need to check if there is still a seam allowance for this line.
After sewing, check if this line is pinned or folded down.
Check the seam allowance and sore.
If it's not, it's still a fold.
We can adjust the size of the skirt and sides.
Now, we make a symmetrical line extension.
After sewing, add these two panels to the inside.
Increase a layer relationship is to ensure that when the back is simulated, this gold panel is inside the sleeve panel.
Apply a new fabric to these two gold panels.
Select this new fabric, and then on the right side of the physical property, you can see that there is an additional elastic band option.
This is a function of our new version of 7.2.
After switching to the elastic band, you can choose the pre-setting of the real elastic band and the shrinked elastic band.
Or we can also find the elastic band in the double-sided fabric at the window here.
Then replace the desired fabric.
These two panels are relatively small, so we need to change the diameter of the elastic band first, and then change the thickness of the gap to 1, and then simulate.
Next, I will show you how to change the length of the elastic band.
Next, we need to make an extension of the two panels below.
Select lines 1 and 2.
Select all directions.
Then here is the movement distance of line 2.
Here is set to 100.
If you want the bottom to be brighter and fly up a little, you can set this movement distance to be a little bigger.
After setting it up, add it to the side to simulate it later.
It's a little more convenient.
After simulating, let's change the back.
Delete this line and then extend it.
The back is the same.
After adding it to the side, this panel is a little bit inserted.
We can pull it out a little bit and simulate it.
This panel is the back.
This is the back side paper that I have to hide.
This is the method of hiding the front of the fabric.
Hide the model.
Next, let's apply a softer fabric to the fabric.
You can also use a softer fabric on your hand.
Then we can apply the front and back pieces of these two small patterned sheets to it into a translucent sand fabric.
You can only see the effect when you open the high-quality
After all is done, we will improve the quality of the clothing.
Thank you for watching.
This step will take you a little longer.
Let's take a look at it.
In addition to the structure of the smocker, the sheets are all back to the fire.
Then the sleeves.
It's all back to the fire.
Next, I'll just simulate the two structures in the middle.
Select thectable, and then turn down its particle diameter to three.
The particle diameter of five is still not very much visible.
The structure of this smocker.
Lower the particle diameter.
But this is also to consider the configuration of the computer.
This step is to increase the effect of a fold.
After opening the fold, the shrinkage will be more delicate.
But at the same time, the computing power will also increase.
In addition to the structure in the middle, the upper and lower parts also need to add a little fold effect.
Let's simulate it.
This simulation will be slower.
Because the particle diameter has been reduced to 3, it is relatively small, and there is an increase in the fold.
But the function of the other side is very simple.
The shape of the fold is a triangle.
And it also creates a predominantly horizontal shape.
Let's write a symbol of the size of the fold.
This symbol's material is the frame.
And it also creates a bring out effect.
Let's write an example.
This symbol is the size of a fold.
Freeze the sleeve
Then the other models that are not involved in the simulation are re-enacted
Reduce computing
The model is re-enacted
Let's see the results
Let's see what happens
In order to see the path below, I hide it
To immerse once
The model fabulous
select the starting point and the end point of the single-click.
Select the side, and then modify its width and conflict thickness.
If you modify the side together, the calculation will be larger.
Display the costume.
After that, save the file.
равtouch
Let's continue to adjust the size of the helmet.
Reduce the PIXEL.
Let's start talking about the second style of work, which is the shirt on our poster.
It's still the same. Let's put the model in first.
Then insert the basic pattern of the shoulder strap into it.
Click to confirm.
Change the pattern based on this pattern.
This style is downloaded from our Kinect website.
Adjust the position of the pattern.
Lock the outer line of the pattern.
Then use the edit pattern tool to select all the internal lines and then convert them into the basic line.
Unlock.
Then the basic line is still locked.
Next, convert the extra points into the free line points.
Or use the edit pattern tool.
Click to confirm.
Then click to convert the upper right button into the free line points.
We can see that the length of the shoulder strap is 184.6 cm.
Then we want the shoulder strap to be lower.
First, select these two shoulder straps.
Then change it to the straight line.
Then modify its length.
Right-click to delete the curve point.
Then change its length.
You can increase it to 40 mm.
That's 224.
Here, pay attention to the direction.
The front and back should be the same length.
The side bones are the same.
Delete its curve point first.
Then drag it to the straight line.
Drag it to the vertical line.
Then, drag it to the right.
Then expand it even more.
Crimp
The shape of the breastbone should still be adjusted.
Adjust the length of the side bone
Then modify the shape of the sleeve
Delete excess curve lines
After adjusting the shape
Then modify the length of the sleeve
Use the multidirectional line tool to measure the length
Because just now
We increased the length of the shoulder line by 40 mm
Here we need to reduce the height of the sleeve by 40 mm
Make a mark first
Then adjust the curve of the sleeve
Delete excess points
Then pull it down directly
Pull it to the mark we made here
Then delete this mark
The length of the sleeve is 436.8 mm
Use the multidirectional line tool
Select all
Then line 1
Which is the sleeve
The curve of the sleeve
Set it to be equal to the length of the sleeve
Then line 2
Which is the edge of the sleeve
We can increase it a little bit
Make the sleeve wider
After extension
You can see it in the 3D window
It's ready
And see here
Set a new pattern
When you look at the model
Rearrange the model
Open the setups
Then rearrange
Next
We stretch thestream black
A little bit
Then change to black
Here is the front and back together, adding 120
This height depends on the style
Next, we will modify the side gap
Rotate this angle
This is 5 degrees
Select the side angle
Then double click to activate the center point
Move the center point to the point above
Then when rotating, press the right button 5 degrees
This ensures that the angle of the front and back pieces is the same
Then adjust the shape of the bottom of the back piece
Use the edit tool to lower the center point
Then switch to edit curve point
Make a curve
Adjust the shape
Here you have to pay attention
Side bones
The front and back pieces here can be connected
Pay attention to their corners
Next, we are going to draw a line here
Then we can directly use the 3D pen tool here at the 3D window
Directly draw a line at the 3D window
Then we go to the base of this line again
To modify
Press the Ctrl button to increase the curve point
Draw a line first
We can see that there is this gray line at the 2D window
Use the 3D pen tool
Adjust the position of this line
And the 3D pen tool
After adjustment, we can open the internal display on the 3D window side to take a look.
Adjusting the line will take some time.
The shortcut key is V, which is easier to use.
Increase the elasticity of the line.
Set the ratio first, and then adjust the effect.
60 is a bit too small.
Increase the size of the curve.
There is a seam on the side of the bone.
It's because we didn't fill in the seam line when we were stretching the clothes.
Now fill it in.
When you set the elasticity, you can look at the front and the bottom to see where the model is.
Adjust the shape here.
Change the fabric to our default fabric and simulate it.
Because this fabric is more suitable for this model.
Adjust the shape.
See the sleeve here.
Next, let's make the structure of this sleeve.
Use the external expansion of the plate.
Expansion can be expanded outward.
It can also be retracted inward.
Use the shrink.
Then set the diameter to 50.
Then we will make another sleeve for it later.
Make it 50.
Use the tool.
The height is 50.
Align it.
The width is 50.
Hold it for 1 minute.
Adjust the volume.
Loosen it.
Fix it.
Put it in the 3D window.
Pay attention to the point where the model's hand is arranged.
The opening of the sleeve cuff goes behind the model's hand.
Next, I will continue to do the X-axis.
The width of the X-axis is 20, and the height is 130.
Use the adjustment board tool to adjust its position.
Then, at the 3D window,
I will first determine the approximate position.
The column is the internal shape.
Then, I will deal with the internal shape.
Here, I have switched to the edit board tool.
Divide these two points.
Then delete the middle line.
These two points add points to the outer line.
Then, I will make another internal line border.
20.
Make a cross-sectional line.
Use the internal multidirectional line tool.
Then, cut it off.
Cut here.
Then, sew up the X-axis.
Use the cross-sectional line.
Finally, there is a point below.
Use the free sewing tool.
Put this 5mm on it.
Switch to the fold.
The lines of this consideration have two explanations before.
Antrag line line to worry the frog tail.
The fan is Costaontal.
And it should be Let maison show you the
If you use the leg line as the corner catching mark,
Something that corresponds to the cross-section...
This is what you can make a cross-sectional line.
This is consistent.
With the qan side.
horr iesss
It is a quick-d 개.
not as long as the cookedilt's
It should be like this.
I look at it, see this big warn's sense.
And you sign a scar.
I bought it
Worldsуш
No millennials want this like this.
Come on.
Because we have adjusted the width of this board, so we need to rearrange it.
We can also adjust the width of the board.
Select the shaker and reduce the width of the board.
The reason for reducing the width of the board is to increase the width of the board.
So we can reduce the width of the board.
And the Shaker position can be reversed.
Right-click to flip the board over.
This is to make sure the middle of the board is outside.
And then we sew this sleeve on
First sew this sleeve separately
Then the rest is sewn together and pressed Shift to sew
Add buttons
Right click on the top of the board
Look at the following positioning
Here up and down can be set to equal length
All 25
Then left, that is, the left side of the board is set to 10
The button button is smaller
Let's adjust its shape here
Choose one you like and then modify the width
Note that the button button and the button button do not turn over
Switch to the button button
Then right click
Up and down are all 25
The distance to the right is 10
Adjust the button button to the corresponding size
Then press the button button
Here we need to add a button button
But I cut the button button
Then show that the bar is at part 1
Then press this button to turn right
Press the button button again
Press this button to turn left
Because there is a button, please be careful
Press this button to click and then press the button between the button button
Lifting January
Then we can see the top and bottom of the video
Over here
This side over here
Both the bottom
The're under level
Add the seam allowance to the sleeve and the seam allowance to the seam allowance.
After adding the buttons, select all the buttons of one sleeve, and then right-click to copy to the version of the symmetrical modification.
You can see that the button of the symmetrical modification has not been added yet.
First, add the symmetrical modification to the outside, and then set the button.
Set the sewing layer.
The button of the 3D window has not been added yet.
Find the button.
Redo the 3D position.
The seam allowance is done.
Confirm the two sides.
Here is a little bit through.
Add it to the outside, and then pull it out a little bit, and then simulate it.
Set the seam allowance.
Next, we will make the front structure.
Use the edit panel tool to cut the seam allowance.
Separate the drawstring position here, and then make a 10mm internal line.
Select the seam allowance.
And then create a 10mm internal line.
Then create a 10mm internal line.
Now make a 10mm internal line.
Select the inner line.
Select and extend the end point.
The two internal lines that are made should also be added to the elastic.
The original one added is 50.
Then these two lines need to be added to the elastic 50.
Look at this.
At this time, the
the particle diameter of the panel is relatively large, so the effect of the draw is not very obvious.
Then move these two small panels to the side, and then combine them.
Let's make a joint.
Then we will make a joint.
And then I'll merge it for him
Choose two to the outside of the board
Then right click to merge
This merge can be done slowly
No need to do it now
Because you can slowly adjust the form later
After merging here
We can see that his symmetry is gone
So if we want to keep this symmetry
Then you can not merge first
Then adjust all the details
And then do this merge at the end
Take a look at the 3D window here
Symmetry is gone
Move it a little
At this time, let's change the fabric for him
Choose the cotton
After changing the fabric, you have to apply it
Choose a foldable board
Then reduce the particle diameter a little
It only goes down to 8 here
Not down to 5 in one breath
After reducing to 8
We can adjust the shape of the foldable part
If it goes directly down to 5
Then it will be more slow to simulate
So first go down to 8
After adjusting this shape
Then to improve the quality of the clothing
And fill it nicely
Then go down to 8
Like this
Then adjust the texture of the foldable
Then continuously turn it over
Next, turn it out a little bit
Then at the end of该
You can see the shape of this pointer
Select these lines
Adjust its proportion
Select the model
Put the model's hand down
Select the model's hand
Move the model
Select the model
Hide the model
Observe the details
Use the fixing pin to fix the middle part first
Then simulate
Put the place that I just said to turn out
Put it in
The shortcut to remove the fixing pin is Ctrl D
Simulate
Ctrl W
Improve the quality of the clothing
Simulation takes a little time
Don't worry
Mark the face
Go to the eye
And look at these details
The Алтар
Select the inner line
It turns out this is the effect of the ALTAR
I will show you the effect of this ALTAR
The height of the interval can be set again
The default here is the direction
After opening the ruler, there is a curve mark
Let's simulate
Add a line to the position of the draw
The interval is 0
Then we want to convert this type from OBJ to text
Select a favorite color
Use white here
Open 3D
Add the line
Add the back piece
The back piece should be dotted twice
It is not symmetrical
The back piece is not symmetrical
The lines are symmetrical
Look at the screen
Adjust the line
Add the line
Draw one line
Adjust the line
The back piece is the same
The back collar is a little deformed
Let's simulate and see the effect
The front collar can be adjusted and lowered
The back collar can be adjusted and lowered
The edit shape line tool here in the 3D window, we can use it to adjust the shape of the collar.
It's more intuitive to adjust it in 3D.
Let's draw the sleeves first.
We only keep the front and back pieces.
Find the desired node
For example, we can use 02 here
This is a duplicate format
But we can
What we want is a VPC format
We can see that there is a clothing file on it
Jpac file folder
Find double click inside
Then find this 02 inside
Add it in
Here you have to choose to increase or not to open
Then click to confirm
Move it to the right position
First, the butterfly is back to the fire
Then adjust this place again
Like this
If you want enough room for butterflies
Adjust his position
Set the position and draw another inner line on the butterfly.
Draw a line with the inner multilinear line tool.
This line is too high, adjust it.
Open the inner line display in the 3D window.
Adjust the position of this line.
This inner line is for sewing.
Sew the butterfly knot with the clothes.
Adjust the position of the inner line.
Use the panel to adjust the position of the inner line.
Adjust the position of the 3D window.
This is to match the seam allowance.
рип
The particle diameter of the蝴蝶結 is relatively small, so it will take a little longer to model.
Choose the middle rope, and then you can add a little bit of shrinkage to it.
Then you can add a little bit of shrinkage to it.
The sound is being simulated.
The freezing is being simulated.
Then you can remove the pin.
Now you can adjust the position of the pin.
Then you can add a little bit of shrinkage to it.
You can remove the pin.
Then you can adjust the position of the pin.
Then copy the butterfly knot
Select it and copy it
Then make a mirror paste
Make a mirror paste
And sew it together
Then look at the 3D window
Select it and adjust the position of the butterfly knot
Then make a mirror paste
After adjusting the position, then copy it
Then look at the 3D window
Select it and adjust the position of the butterfly knot
Make a mirror paste
And sew it together
Then look at the 3D window
Make a mirror paste
Then close the display of the internal line
Then let's simulate together
Press 5 and then select all panels to adjust this position
Because I just found that this dress is a little bit too flat, I can move it a little bit more
After moving it, I will simulate it again
Here at the neck, you can choose the neck circle
Choose the center of the circle and then open the elastic
The proportion is 100%
Then add a sticker to the neck
Hide the model
Add a circle of stickers
And then add a sticker to the side
At the right, in the element editor, you can adjust the width
Make it smaller
Note that the conflict thickness needs to be adjusted
After adjusting, simulate
Add a sticker to the bottom
If you add it directly
You can see that this place is more difficult to locate
Because it was blocked by the butterfly knot
And then we will attach it
Then we are going to add a sticker to the bottom
Add a sticker to the top
Add a sticker to the bottom
Then we just add it
I will give you the status of the first point and the last point
Hide the butterfly knot
Then use the
This will make it easier to determine the starting and ending points
End point double
Change the conflict thickness to 1
Add the front piece as well.
After adding the front piece, you need to adjust the thickness of the seam allowance.
Then, apply the seam allowance again.
At this time, it's a little stuck, it doesn't matter if it's penetrated, choose this edge,
Re-activate it first, and then modify the volume to make it more realistic.
That is, add it again to the inside, and then modify it.
Show all the clothing.
Look at this butterfly knot, and adjust the length of the tail of the butterfly knot.
If you adjust it directly, you will find that its end is not visible.
In this case, you can adjust the length of the tail, if you do not want to show the tip, you can adjust the length of the tail, if you do not want to show the tip.
Both sides will change at the same time
Because it is a symmetrical version
So we have to remove its link first
Choose to remove link
Then switch back to the edit version tool
Adjust its length
The same goes for this side
First, remove the link
Then adjust its length
After stretching, right-click to set the distance of movement
Then click on the center in the search bar
To adjust its length
Then click on the center by clicking on the center button
Tap on the center button
Check its image
Find its image
Tap on the center to change its color
You can enter the color you want
When summer comes, you can choose a color you like
After choosing the application, you can see that the costume has also changed
Then we put other corresponding buttons, buttons, eyes, and bright lines
Apply the same color to it
Select this color
The application
Then let's take a look
In order to make the bright line here more obvious
We can add bright colors on the bright line
Then we click on it
After that, click on the application and turn it off, and the butterfly knot hasn't changed color yet.
Apply it.
So the costume is basically done.
Next, save the file.